Nav
---

* ### Send & Receive
    
    * [Financial Education
        
        (opens in a new tab)](https://venmo.com/about/us/financial-education/ "Financial Education")
    
* ### Pay with Venmo

* ### Venmo for Business

### Send & Receive

### Pay with Venmo

### Venmo for Business

* * *

### Resources

### Company

Privacy Statement
=================

**DATE EFFECTIVE**

May 12, 2024

Please [click here](#teen-users) to learn how we manage information about Teen Users.

**OUR COMMITMENT TO PRIVACY**

Venmo, a PayPal, Inc. service, knows that you care about how your personal information is used and disclosed, and we take your privacy seriously. Our primary goal is to provide you with exceptional service, and we understand that you may have questions or concerns regarding your personal information and how it will be used. To make this Privacy Statement easy to find, we make it available from the home page of the Venmo website at [**venmo.com**](https://venmo.com/) (the "website") and through our mobile applications. You may also email us at [**privacy@venmo.com**](mailto:%20privacy@venmo.com) with any privacy-related questions you have.

**APPLICABILITY OF PRIVACY STATEMENT**

This Privacy Statement applies to all information we collect through our Services from current and former Venmo users. “Services” means any products, services, content, features, technologies, or functions, and all related websites, applications and services offered to you by PayPal, Inc. in connection with a Venmo account. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to disclose your information as described in this Statement. This Statement only applies to the Services and does not apply to the practices of any other PayPal service.

Venmo is always improving. As the Services evolve we may occasionally update this Privacy Statement to reflect changes to our business, Services, or applicable laws. If the revised version requires notice in accordance with applicable law, we will provide you with 30 days prior notice by posting notice of the change on the "**Privacy Statement**" page of our website and mobile apps, otherwise the revised Privacy Statement will be effective as of the published effective date. If you are a new customer or are receiving this Privacy Statement for the first time and there is an upcoming change described on the “Privacy Statement” page of our website and mobile app at the time you receive this Privacy Statement, such upcoming change will apply to you on the indicated effective date.

Throughout this Privacy Statement, we use the term "personal information" to describe information that can be associated with a specific person and can be used to identify that person. We do not consider personal information to include information that has been aggregated and/or anonymized so that it does not identify a specific person.

This Privacy Statement also applies to all information we collect from non-Venmo users who receive a payment from Venmo users through the Visa+ Service (the “Recipient”).

The Visa+ Service enables customers, with an eligible Venmo account, to send and receive money to and from PayPal and third-party Visa+-enabled digital wallets (“Visa+”).

**THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

When you visit the website or use one of our mobile applications or other Services, we collect your IP address, and standard web log information, such as your browser type and the pages you accessed on our website. We also may collect Geolocation Information (defined below). If you do not agree to our collection of this information, you may not be able to use our Service.

If you open a Venmo account, we collect the following information from you:

* Account Information - text-enabled cellular/wireless telephone number, machine or mobile device ID and other similar information.
    
* Identification Information - your name, street address, email address, date of birth, and Social Security number ("SSN") (or other governmental issued verification numbers).
    
* Device Information - information about you: (a) from your mobile device or computer such as your device type, machine or mobile device identification number, Geolocation Information, time zone, language setting, browser type, and IP address, and (b) from third parties for purposes of transaction processing, identity verification, fraud detection or prevention and other similar purposes. For fraud prevention purposes, we also may link your machine ID with the machines of others who use your same payment cards.
    
* Geolocation Information - information that identifies with reasonable specificity your location by using, for instance, longitude and latitude coordinates obtained through GPS, Wi-Fi, or cell site triangulation. We will collect this data for fraud and risk purposes. In addition, some of our Services may ask you for permission to disclose your current location within your device settings to enhance our Services. If you do not agree to our collection of Geolocation Information, our Services may not function properly when you try to use them. For information about your ability to restrict the collection and use of Geolocation Information to enhance our Services, please refer to the settings available in your device.
    
* Social Web Information - with your consent, we may also collect information from social networks, such as your Facebook Connect credentials and email account information. If you authorize Facebook Connect, the plug in allows us access to your email address, Facebook friends list, and public profile (including profile picture). We also allow you to import data from other social web services, including but not limited to Twitter, FourSquare, and email service providers. Social and e-mail contact information helps you connect to friends and contacts for invitation and payment transmission purposes (as well as helping us improve the Services and fight fraud). Additionally, another Venmo user may mention you in a transaction to which you are not a party by “tagging” your username in a transaction note or comment. When you are mentioned in a transaction note or comment into which you have visibility (e.g., a public transaction, a “friends only” transaction by one of your Venmo friends, or a comment on either such transaction), a link to your Venmo profile will appear in the transaction note or comment and, if your push notifications are turned on, you will receive a push notification about the mentions. You may manage certain contact preferences and notifications in your account settings.
    
* Financial Information - bank account online login information, bank account and routing numbers and credit cards linked to your Venmo account. Venmo does not disclose financial information with third party social networking services such as those listed in the prior bullet.
    
* Biometric Information - when you consent in the user experience, we collect face scans to authenticate your account and manage fraud and risk.
    
* Audio, electronic, visual or similar information - Call recordings when you talk to customer service or sales.
    
* Professional or employment information – including business information, contact emails, phone numbers and taxpayer ID numbers.
    
* Information you provide when you contact us – your response to surveys, recorded conversations, chat conversations with us, email correspondence with us, account status, repayment history, information about others if you choose to share it with us.

We may also collect the above data from other third parties, including service providers, internet service providers, partners and merchants, credit reporting agencies, government entities, data brokers, data analytics providers, advertising networks, card networks and financial institutions.

In particular, for Visa+ we will receive the Recipient’s name and payment information from Visa and third-party Visa+ participating digital wallets for the purpose of processing and matching Visa+ payment transactions between participating digital wallets and Venmo.

We are committed to providing a safe, secure and all-around great service. Therefore, before permitting you to use the Services, we may require additional information from you we can use to verify your identity, address or other information in order to comply with law or to manage risk and compliance throughout our relationship. We may also obtain information about you from third parties such as identity verification, fraud prevention and similar services.

When you are using the Services, we collect information about your account transactions and we may collect Geolocation Information and/or information about your computer or your operating systems or other access device for fraud prevention and other similar purposes.

Finally, we may collect additional information from or about you in other ways not specifically described here. For example, we may collect information related to your contact with our customer support team, store results when you respond to a survey, or when you use PayPal or another PayPal service.

**INFORMATION FROM CHILDREN**

The Services are not directed to children under the age of 13. If we obtain actual knowledge that we have collected personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will promptly delete it, unless we are legally obligated to retain such data. [Contact us](https://help.venmo.com/hc/en-us/requests/new) if you believe that we have mistakenly or unintentionally collected information from a child under the age of 13.

**INFORMATION FOR AND ABOUT TEEN USERS**

In this section we explain how we handle your data if you use a Venmo Teen Account. We may offer an account holder (“Account Holder”) the opportunity to create a Venmo Teen Account for use by an authorized individual between the ages of 13 and 17 years old at account creation (“Teen User”). We will not collect more information about you than what is required to use the Teen Account.

**What data do we collect?**

**Identifiers**: An Account Holder provides your name, birthday, address, and phone number. You will create a username/password for online account access. You will also provide your email address when you sign up for access to the app. When you use your Teen Account, you can make changes to your name that is displayed to other users.  
  
**Device Information**: Information about your mobile device or computer such as your device type and IP address.  
  
**Internet or network activity**: Interactions with our Services, Information about response time for web pages, download errors, date and time when you used the Teen Account, statistics regarding how pages are loaded or viewed, and other usage information.

**Why do we collect your data?**  
  
To provide our Services: We only collect data from Teen Users that is necessary to interact with the Teen Account, such as to enable you to send or receive money or use Venmo as payment method at checkout at an authorized merchant's website or mobile app or in-person by using a Venmo QR code.  
  
To manage and improve our Services: We collect data to conduct customer analysis, provide our Services, and to support internal operations, for example troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, and statistical purposes.

**Do we disclose your data?**  
  
We may need to disclose data to other parties. Disclose means that other people may see your information. For example, we may disclose the name you have chosen to display to other users when you make a payment to them.

Your data is disclosed with the Account Holder: the Account Holder will be able to monitor and access your activities and manage your user and privacy settings.

We disclose your data with The Bancorp Bank, N.A. and Mastercard in order to provide you with the Debit Card services. We may disclose data with merchants when you use your Venmo account to make a purchase. We may also disclose data with service providers that help us with our internal operations and analysis at our direction, such as processing payments, ensuring compliance, audits, corporate governance, communications, IT development, and maintenance.

We may disclose your information or data with other parties. Depending on the settings an Account Holder chooses, your information or data might be seen by your friends, friends of the other party to the transaction or the public. We may also disclose your data with third parties if there is a legal obligation to do so.  
  
**Teen User Data Requests**  
  
Along with the Account Holder, you may review the personal information we have about you. You may also request your data be corrected if it is wrong or have it deleted.

If you would like to exercise your access rights, please log on to your account through the browser and submit the data access requests under the privacy link. For all other data subject rights, please contact us by clicking [here](https://help.venmo.com/hc/en-us/requests/new).  
  
**Account Holder Rights**  
  
The Account Holder has the right to review the personal information collected online from their Teen User; refuse to allow further use or online collection of personal information from their Teen User; and request the deletion of the personal information collected online from their Teen User (unless we are required to retain it). If an Account Holder doesn’t want us to continue to collect or use their Teen User’s personal information, or if an Account Holder asks us to delete it, we will remove their Teen User’s online profile and close their Teen User’s account. Account Holders that wish to exercise their Teen User access rights, please log on to your account through the browser and submit the data access requests under the privacy link. For all other data subject rights, please contact us by [clicking here](https://help.venmo.com/hc/en-us/requests/new?ticket_form_id=624807). The Account Holder will have the ability to control their Teen User’s transaction privacy settings, their visibility on friends’ list and the ability to block users. The Account Holder can make these changes by selecting the Teen account profile in the app.

A Teen User will get alerts and notifications about some activities in their account. Please note that the Account Holder will also receive messages about a Teen User’s activity, such as completed transactions and when a Teen User saves Venmo as a payment method with a merchant.

**HOW WE USE COOKIES**

When you visit or use our Services, or visit a third-party website for which we provide online services, we and certain business partners and vendors may use cookies and other tracking technologies (collectively, "Cookies"). We use Cookies to recognize you as a customer; customize Services, other content and advertising, measure the effectiveness of promotions, perform a wide range of analytics, mitigate risk and prevent potential fraud, and to promote trust and safety across our Services.

Certain Services are only available through the use of Cookies, so if you choose to disable or decline Cookies, your use of certain Services may be limited or not possible.

Do Not Track: Do Not Track ("DNT") is an optional browser setting that allows you to express your preferences regarding tracking by advertisers and other third parties. We do not respond to DNT signals.

Please review our Statement on Cookies and Tracking Technologies to learn more about how we use Cookies.

**HOW WE PROTECT & STORE PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We store and process your personal information using third party servers located in data centers in the United States. This information is protected by physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in compliance with applicable US federal and state laws and regulations. We also use computer safeguards such as firewalls and data encryption, we enforce physical access controls to our office and files, and we authorize access to personal information only for those employees who require it to fulfill their job responsibilities.

We strive to ensure security on our systems. Despite our efforts, we cannot guarantee that personal information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of our administrative, managerial and technical safeguards. Therefore, we urge you to take adequate precautions to protect your personal information as well, including never sharing your Venmo password with anyone.

If Venmo learns of a systems security breach, we may attempt to notify you electronically so you can take appropriate protective steps. By using the Services, you agree that Venmo may communicate with you electronically. Venmo may post a notice on the website or mobile applications if a security breach occurs. We may also send an email to you at the email address you have provided to us. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice of a security breach), please email us at [privacy@venmo.com](mailto: privacy@venmo.com)

**HOW LONG WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We retain your Personal Information for as long as needed or permitted in context of the purpose for which it was collected and consistent with applicable law.

The criteria used to determine our retention period is as follows:

* Personal Information used for the ongoing relationship between you and Venmo is stored for the duration of the relationship plus a period of 10 years, unless we need to keep it longer, such as:
    
    * a legal obligation or compliance with laws to which we are subject is retained consistent with the applicable law, such as under Anti-Money Laundering obligations
        
    * litigation, investigations, audit, and compliance practices, or to protect against legal claims.

**HOW WE USE THE PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

Our primary business purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, fun and customized experience. We may use your personal information to:

* provide the Services and customer support you request;
    
* process transactions and match payments, including payments performed by you through Visa+ when paying non-Venmo users and matching of such payments to participating digital wallets, and to send notices about your transactions or your network activity;
    
* resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems;
    
* prevent potentially fraudulent, prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our User Agreement through the use of our risk and fraud tools which may include use of Account Information, Identification Information, Financial Information, Device Information, Social Web Information and Geolocation Information;
    
* create an account connection between your Venmo account and a third-party account or platform;
    
* customize, personalize, measure, and improve our services and the content and layout of our website, including showing you location-based promotions and business profiles;
    
* send you updates about new products and services that we are offering to customers;
    
* compare information for accuracy and verify it with third parties;
    
* perform other duties as required by law;
    
* if you elect to disclose your Geolocation Information, we will use this information to enhance the security of the Services and we may use this information to provide you with location-based options, functionality, offers, advertising, search results, or other location-based content;
    
* if you have a business profile, you can choose to use your address to offer location-based promotions to Venmo users near you; and
    
* if you use one of the following services: PayPal and PayPal Honey; we may associate information about your transactions and experiences using these services to personalize content and offers and improve your use of the Venmo Services.  

**HOW WE DISCLOSE PERSONAL INFORMATION WITHIN THE VENMO NETWORK**

To process payments on Venmo, we need to disclose some of your personal information with the person or company that you are paying or is paying you. Your contact information, date of sign-up, the number of payments you have received and other verification metrics like social graph activity may be provided to users or companies when you transact with, on, or through Venmo.

We work with vendors to enable them to accept payments from you using Venmo. In doing so, a vendor may disclose information about you with us, such as your mobile phone number or Venmo username, when you attempt to pay that vendor. We use this information to confirm to that vendor that you are a Venmo customer and that the vendor should enable Venmo as a form of payment for your purchase.

Regardless, we will not disclose your credit card number or bank account number to anyone you have paid or who has paid you through Venmo, except with your express permission or if we are required to do so in order to comply with a subpoena or other legal process.

**HOW WE DISCLOSE PERSONAL INFORMATION WITH OTHER PARTIES**

Venmo does not disclose your personal information with third parties for their promotional or marketing purposes.

Some personal information is public information and may be seen by anyone on the internet, whether or not they have a Venmo account. Public information may also be seen, accessed, reshared or downloaded through Venmo's APIs or third-party services that integrate with our products.

* Public information for personal profiles includes your Venmo username, profile photo, first and last name, month and year of Venmo account creation, and public transactions in which you've been involved.
    
* Public information for business or charity profiles includes Venmo username, profile and background photos, business or charity name, business or charity description, and QR code.
    
* Public information for business or charity profiles may be indexed by and searchable on search engines.

In addition to any public information, your Venmo friends list may be seen by any logged-in Venmo user; you may adjust or turn off this setting in the privacy section in your account settings.

We may disclose your personal information with:

* Our parent company, PayPal, Inc. and affiliates and subsidiaries it controls, but only for purposes allowed by this document.
    
* Companies that PayPal, Inc. plans to merge with or be acquired by or, in the event of any bankruptcy, a bankruptcy estate. Should such a combination occur, we will require that the new combined entity follow this Privacy Statement with respect to your personal information. If your personal information could be used contrary to this Statement, you will receive prior notice and the opportunity to communicate preferences you may have, if applicable.
    
* Law enforcement, government officials, or other third parties if PayPal is compelled to do so by a subpoena, court order or similar legal procedure; when it is necessary to do so to comply with law; or where the disclosure of personal information is reasonably necessary to prevent physical harm or financial loss, to report suspected illegal activity, or to investigate violations of the Venmo User Agreement, or as otherwise required by law.
    
* Third party service providers who assist us in providing Services to you or who provide fraud detection or similar services on our or any vendor’s behalf.
    
* The other Venmo user participating in the transaction and, depending on the privacy setting of each Venmo account transaction, your Venmo friends and the Venmo friends of the other user participating in the transaction, or the public, through the Venmo feed on our website and mobile application and elsewhere on the internet. For transactions and activity made with other Venmo users using a groups feature, the other Venmo users in that group will be able to see your transactions and activity.
    
* Businesses when you follow their business profile. We will share your name with a business when you follow their profile.
    
* Service providers under contract who help with parts of our business operations (for example, fraud prevention, payment processing, or technology services). Our contracts dictate that these service providers only use your information in connection with the services they perform for us and not for their own benefit.
    
* Partners and merchants, their service providers and others involved in a transaction, for example when you use the Services to initiate online purchases, pay non-Venmo users through Visa+ or return goods, we may disclose information about you and your Venmo account with the other parties (or their service providers) involved in processing your transactions. We may also disclose Personal Information to partners and merchants to enable their use of our Services to facilitate your transactions. For example, when you visit a participating merchant site or app, the merchant can check whether you are a user of PayPal services and present a recommended payment method to you to simplify your checkout process. Please note that personal information shared with partners and merchants (or their service providers) involved in a transaction is subject to the partners’ and merchants’ own privacy policy and procedures.  
    
* For our businesses and their beneficial owners, we report personal information to databases maintained by the card networks pursuant to the card scheme rules to fulfill listing and reporting obligations.
    
* Other users if you have a business profile. You may choose to display certain information about your business profile on the Venmo network, such as your street address, phone number, email, social media accounts and website. You can control how this information is displayed in your business profile settings. We will also disclose certain information about your business profile to other users, such as how long ago your business profile was created, total number of subscribers, and total number of transactions. We may also use your address, transaction activity and engagement activity on Venmo to rank your business relative to other businesses in your area.
    
* Other third parties with your consent or at your direction to do so, including if you authorize an account connection with a third-party account or platform.
    
    * For the purposes of this Privacy Statement, an "account connection" with such a third party is a connection you authorize or enable between your Venmo account and a non-Venmo account, payment instrument, or platform that you lawfully control or own. When you authorize such a connection, Venmo and the third-party will exchange your personal information and other information directly. Examples of account connections include, without limitation: linking your Venmo account to a social media account or social messaging service; connecting your Venmo account to a third-party data aggregation or financial services company, if you provide such company with your Venmo account log-in credentials; or using your Venmo account to make payments to a merchant or allowing a merchant to charge your Venmo account.
        
    * If you connect your Venmo account to other financial accounts, directly or through a third-party service provider, we may have access to your account balance and account and transactional information, such as purchases and funds transfers. If you choose to create an account connection, we may receive information from the third-party about you and your use of the third-party’s service. For example, if you connect your Venmo account to a social media account, we will receive personal information from the social media provider via the account connection. We will use all such information that we receive from a third-party via an account connection in a manner consistent with this Privacy Statement.
        
    * Information that we disclose with a third-party based on an account connection will be used and disclosed in accordance with the third-party’s privacy practices. Before authorizing an account connection, you should review the privacy notice of any third-party that will gain access to your personal information as part of the account connection. For example, personal information that Venmo discloses with a third-party account or platform such as a social media account may in turn be disclosed with certain other parties, including the general public, depending on the account’s or platform’s privacy practices.
        
    * If you choose to use Siri or iMessage to send payments via Venmo or to otherwise use the Services, such use is subject to Apple’s terms and conditions for use of iMessage and/or Siri, as applicable, and the terms of the Venmo User Agreement. By using Siri or iMessage, you authorize us to disclose some of your Venmo account data (including your friends list, list of persons you have transacted with most recently and most frequently, transaction instructions, and transaction notes) with Apple to allow it to facilitate transaction requests made through Siri or iMessage on iOS. Data disclosed with Apple will be used pursuant to Apple’s then-current user agreements and privacy policies. You can grant or revoke Apple’s access to Venmo on iOS at any time under the “Siri” or “iMessage” settings on your iPhone.

Venmo does not send your personal information to third-party social networks unless you have specifically requested or authorized us to do so. When you broadcast information to such third-party social networks, such information is no longer under the control of Venmo and is subject to the terms of use and privacy policies of such third parties.

**HOW YOU CAN ACCESS OR CHANGE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

You can review and update your personal information in your account settings at any time by logging in to your account.

**LINKS TO OTHER SERVICES OR SITES**

The Services may contain links to (or allow you to link to) other third-party services or websites. Venmo does not control the information collection of third-party services or websites that can be reached through such links. We encourage our users to be aware when they are linking to a third-party service or website and to read the privacy statements of any third-party service or website that collects personally identifiable information.

**HOW TO CONTACT US**

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Statement, or any feedback pertaining to your privacy and the Services that you would like us to consider, please email us at [privacy@venmo.com](mailto: privacy@venmo.com)

### Consumer Privacy Notice

Venmo is a service provided by PayPal, Inc. (“Venmo”). The following Consumer Privacy Notice applies to you if you are an individual who resides in the United States and use the Services for your own personal, family or household purposes.

|     | What does Venmo do with your personal information? |
| --- | --- |
| **Why?** | Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do. |
| **What?** | The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have or you may use with us. This information can include:<br><br>* Social Security number and account balances<br>    <br>* Payment history or transaction history<br>    <br>* Credit history or credit scores<br>    <br><br>When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice. |
| **How?** | All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons Venmo chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing. |

| **Reasons we can share your personal information** | Does Venmo share? | **Can you limit this sharing?** |
| --- | --- | --- |
| **For our everyday business purposes—**<br><br>such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus | Yes | No  |
| **For our marketing purposes—**<br><br>to offer our products and services to you | Yes | No  |
| **For joint marketing with other financial companies** | Yes | No  |
| **For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—**<br><br>information about your transactions and experiences | Yes | No  |
| **For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—**<br><br>information about your creditworthiness | No  | We don’t share |
| **For our affiliates to market to you** | No  | We don’t share |
| **For nonaffiliates to market to you** | No  | We don’t share |

| Additional Information |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Who is providing this Privacy Policy?** | This privacy notice is provided by Venmo, a service of PayPal, Inc. in connection with its provision of Venmo, and is applicable to your personal Venmo account. |
| **How does Venmo protect my personal information?** | To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings. |
| **How does Venmo collect my personal information?** | We collect your personal information, for example, when you<br><br>* open an account or provide account information<br>    <br>* link your credit or debit card to your Venmo account or give us your contact information<br>    <br>* use your Venmo account to send or receive funds<br>    <br><br>We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, partners and merchants, or other companies. |
| **Why can’t I limit all sharing?** | Federal law gives you the right to limit only<br><br>* sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes— information about your creditworthiness<br>    <br>* affiliates from using your information to market to you<br>    <br>* sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you<br>    <br><br>State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing. See below for more information on your rights under state law. |

| **Definitions** |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Affiliates** | Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.<br><br>* Our affiliates include Bill Me Later, Inc. |
| **Nonaffiliates** | Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.<br><br>* Nonaffiliates with which we share personal information include service providers that perform services or functions on our behalf. |
| **Joint Marketing** | A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.<br><br>* Our joint marketing partners include financial companies and banks. |

| **California and Vermont Information** |
| --- |
| We may transfer personal information to other countries, for example, for customer service or to process transactions.<br><br>**California:**   <br>The California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) permits consumers who are California residents to ask businesses covered under the CCPA about personal information it has collected about the consumer, submit an access or deletion request, and opt-out of the “sale” or “sharing” of personal information, if applicable. These provisions do not apply to personal information collected, processed, shared, or disclosed by financial institutions pursuant to federal law such as the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act. Contact us if you have questions about our privacy statement, this consumer notice, or your personal information. If your Venmo account has a California mailing address, we will not share personal information we collect about you except to the extent permitted under California law.<br><br>**Vermont:  <br>**If your Venmo account has a Vermont mailing address, we will not share personal information we collect about you with non-affiliates unless the law allows or you provide authorization. We will not disclose information about your creditworthiness to our affiliates and will not disclose your personal information, financial information, credit report, or health information to nonaffiliated third parties to market to you, other than as permitted by Vermont law, unless you authorize us to make those disclosures. Additional information concerning our privacy policies can be found at _https://venmo.com/legal/us-licenses/_ or call [**1-855-812-4430**](tel:+18558124430). |

### California Consumer Privacy Act Notice

**California Consumer Privacy Act Notice**

If you are a California resident, the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”) requires us to provide you with the following additional information about: (1) the business purpose for which we use each category of “personal information” including “sensitive personal information” (as defined in the CCPA) we collect; and (2) the categories of third parties to which we (a) disclose such personal information for a business purpose, (b) “share” personal information for “cross-context behavioral advertising,” and/or (c) “sell” such personal information.

Under California law, “sharing” is defined as the targeting of advertising to a consumer based on that consumer’s personal information obtained from the consumer’s activity across websites, and “selling” is defined as the disclosure of personal information to third parties in exchange for monetary or other valuable consideration. We do not sell or share your Personal Information, including any Sensitive Personal Information.

This notice should be read together with Venmo’s Privacy Statement and applies to all California residents who visit our Sites or use the Services.

**Personal Information Collection and Purposes of Use**

We collect, use and disclose personal information regarding California residents as described in this notice.

**We did not sell or share any consumers’ personal information, including sensitive personal information. This includes personal information about anyone under 16 years of age.**

**California Residents’ Privacy Rights**

California residents and residents of other certain states (such as Virginia) have rights to request access to certain personal information collected about them over the past 12 months, right to correct your personal information, right to opt out of the sale or sharing of personal information, right to limit the use or disclosure of sensitive personal information, or the right to deletion of their personal information, subject to certain exceptions, and may not be discriminated against because they exercise any of their rights under the California Consumer Privacy Act.

If you or an authorized agent submit a request, we’ll first need to verify who you are before we can respond to your request. We may ask you to provide us with information necessary to reasonably verify your identity before responding to your request. We will compare the information you submit against our internal business records to verify your identity. If we can’t verify your identity, we will not be able to fulfill your request. If we deny your request in whole or in part, you may have the right to appeal the decision. In such circumstances, we will provide you with information regarding the appeals process.

Global Privacy Control setting is a browser setting that notifies website owners of users' privacy preferences regarding selling or sharing their personal information. Venmo does not respond to these settings because we do not sell or share data.

You or your authorized agent may contact us by clicking [**here**](https://help.venmo.com/hc/en-us/requests/new) or call us at [**1-855-812-4430**](tel:+18558124430). Learn more about how we have handled your [**Privacy Rights**](https://www.paypal.com/us/legalhub/ca-privacy-rights-full?locale.x=en_US).

| **We have collected the following categories of personal information from California Residents:** | **We have collected such personal information from the following categories of sources:** | **We collected such personal information to use for the following purposes:** | **We disclosed such personal information with the following categories of third parties for business purpose:** |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| A. Identifiers such as a real name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, social security number, driver’s license number, passport number, or other similar identifiers. | * from you when you use our Services<br>    <br>* partners and merchants<br>    <br>* service providers<br>    <br>* financial institutions<br>    <br>* social networks, with your consent<br>    <br>* advertising networks | * provide the Services and customer support<br>    <br>* process and match transactions and send notices about your transactions or your network activity<br>    <br>* resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems<br>    <br>* prevent potentially fraudulent, prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our User Agreement<br>    <br>* create an account connection between your Venmo account and a third-party account or platform<br>    <br>* customize, personalize, measure, and improve our services and the content and layout of our website and send you or Venmo users location-based options<br>    <br>* send you updates about new products and services that we are offering to customers<br>    <br>* compare information for accuracy and verify it with third parties<br>    <br>* perform other duties as required by law | * PayPal, Inc. and affiliates and subsidiaries it controls<br>    <br>* service providers<br>    <br>* financial institutions and databases maintained by card networks<br>    <br>* partners and merchants<br>    <br>* third party accounts or platforms<br>    <br>* parties to the transaction<br>    <br>* other Venmo users<br>    <br>* internet users (some personal information is public information including your Venmo username, Venmo profile photo, Venmo profile first and last name, month, and year of Venmo account creation, and public transactions in which you’ve been involved, and may be seen by anyone on the internet, whether or not they have a Venmo account)<br>    <br>* third parties for our business purposes or as permitted or required by law<br>    <br>* law enforcement, government officials, or other third parties |
| B. Any categories of personal information described in subdivision (e) of Section 1798.80: “Personal information” means any information that identifies, relates to, describes, or is capable of being associated with, a particular individual, including, but not limited to, his or her name, signature, social security number, physical characteristics or description, address, telephone number, passport number, driver’s license or state identification card number, education, employment, employment history, bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, or any other financial information, medical information. “Personal information” does not include publicly available information that is lawfully made available to the general public from federal, state, or local government records. | * from you when you use our Services<br>    <br>* partners and merchants<br>    <br>* service providers<br>    <br>* financial institutions | * provide the Services and customer support<br>    <br>* process transactions and send notices about your transactions or your network activity<br>    <br>* resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems<br>    <br>* prevent potentially fraudulent, prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our User Agreement<br>    <br>* create an account connection between your Venmo account and a third-party account or platform<br>    <br>* customize, personalize, measure, and improve our services and the content and layout of our website and send you or Venmo users location-based options<br>    <br>* send you updates about new products and services that we are offering to customers<br>    <br>* compare information for accuracy and verify it with third parties<br>    <br>* perform other duties as required by law | * PayPal, Inc. and affiliates and subsidiaries it controls<br>    <br>* service providers<br>    <br>* financial institutions<br>    <br>* partners and merchants<br>    <br>* third party accounts or platforms<br>    <br>* parties to the transaction<br>    <br>* other Venmo users<br>    <br>* internet users (some personal information is public information including your Venmo username, Venmo profile photo, Venmo profile first and last name, month, and year of Venmo account creation, and public transactions in which you’ve been involved, and may be seen by anyone on the internet, whether or not they have a Venmo account)<br>    <br>* third parties for our business purposes or as permitted or required by law<br>    <br>* law enforcement, government officials, or other third parties |
| C. Characteristics of protected classifications under California or federal law, including age or date of birth, national origin, disability, citizenship, military status. | * from you when you use our Services<br>    <br>* service providers | * provide the Services<br>    <br>* prevent potentially fraudulent, prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our User Agreement<br>    <br>* send you updates about new products and services that we are offering to customers<br>    <br>* compare information for accuracy and verify it with third parties<br>    <br>* perform other duties as required by law | * PayPal, Inc. and affiliates and subsidiaries it controls<br>    <br>* service providers<br>    <br>* financial institutions<br>    <br>* third parties for our business purposes or as permitted or required by law<br>    <br>* law enforcement, government officials, or other third parties |
| D. Commercial information, including products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies. | * from you when you use our Services<br>    <br>* partners and merchants<br>    <br>* service providers<br>    <br>* financial institution<br>    <br>* Other Venmo users if you have a business profile | * provide the Services and customer support<br>    <br>* process transactions and send notices about your transactions or your network activity<br>    <br>* resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems<br>    <br>* prevent potentially fraudulent, prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our User Agreement<br>    <br>* create an account connection between your Venmo account and a third-party account or platform<br>    <br>* customize, personalize, measure, and improve our services and the content and layout of our website<br>    <br>* send you updates about new products and services that we are offering to customers<br>    <br>* compare information for accuracy and verify it with third parties<br>    <br>* perform other duties as required by law | * PayPal, Inc. and affiliates and subsidiaries it controls<br>    <br>* service providers<br>    <br>* financial institutions<br>    <br>* partners and merchants<br>    <br>* third party accounts or platforms<br>    <br>* parties to the transaction<br>    <br>* other Venmo users<br>    <br>* internet users (some personal information is public information including your Venmo username, Venmo profile photo, Venmo profile first and last name, month, and year of Venmo account creation, and public transactions in which you’ve been involved, and may be seen by anyone on the internet, whether or not they have a Venmo account)<br>    <br>* third parties for our business purposes or as permitted or required by law<br>    <br>* law enforcement, government officials, or other third parties |
| E. Internet or other electronic network activity information, including, but not limited to, browsing history, search history, and information regarding a consumer’s interaction with an Internet Web site, application, or advertisement. | * from you when you use our Services<br>    <br>* partners and merchants<br>    <br>* service providers<br>    <br>* operating systems | * provide the Services and customer support<br>    <br>* process transactions and send notices about your transactions or your network activity<br>    <br>* resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems<br>    <br>* prevent potentially fraudulent, prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our User Agreement<br>    <br>* create an account connection between your Venmo account and a third-party account or platform<br>    <br>* customize, personalize, measure, and improve our services and the content and layout of our website<br>    <br>* send you updates about new products and services that we are offering to customers<br>    <br>* compare information for accuracy and verify it with third parties<br>    <br>* perform other duties as required by law | * PayPal, Inc. and affiliates and subsidiaries it controls<br>    <br>* service providers<br>    <br>* financial institutions<br>    <br>* third party accounts or platforms<br>    <br>* third parties for our business purposes or as permitted or required by law<br>    <br>* law enforcement, government officials, or other third parties |
| F. Geolocation data, with consent. | * from you if you elect to disclose this information<br>    <br>* service providers | * to enhance the security of Services, provide you with location-based options, functionality, offers, advertising, search results, or other location-based content<br>    <br>* prevent potentially fraudulent, prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our User Agreement | * PayPal, Inc. and affiliates and subsidiaries it controls<br>    <br>* service providers<br>    <br>* third parties for our business purposes or as permitted or required by law<br>    <br>* law enforcement, government officials, or other third parties |
| G. Audio, electronic, visual, or similar information. | * from you when you use our Services | * provide the Services and customer support<br>    <br>* process transactions<br>    <br>* resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems<br>    <br>* prevent potentially fraudulent, prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our User Agreement<br>    <br>* compare information for accuracy and verify it with third parties<br>    <br>* perform other duties as required by law | * PayPal, Inc. and affiliates and subsidiaries it controls<br>    <br>* service providers<br>    <br>* third parties for our business purposes or as permitted or required by law<br>    <br>* law enforcement, government officials, or other third parties |
| H. Biometric information | * From you when you consent and request certain services from | * Provide the Services<br>    <br>* Prevent potentially fraudulent, prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our User Agreement<br>    <br>* Perform other duties as required by law | * Service Providers |
| I. Inferences drawn from any of the information identified in this subdivision to create a profile about a consumer reflecting the consumer’s preferences, characteristics, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, and abilities. | * from you when you use our Services<br>    <br>* partners and merchants<br>    <br>* service providers | * provide the Services<br>    <br>* prevent potentially fraudulent, prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our User Agreement<br>    <br>* customize, personalize, measure, and improve our services and the content and layout of our website<br>    <br>* send you updates about new products and services that we are offering to customers<br>    <br>* perform other duties as required by law | * PayPal, Inc. and affiliates and subsidiaries it controls<br>    <br>* service providers<br>    <br>* third parties for our business purposes or as permitted or required by law<br>    <br>* law enforcement, government officials, or other third parties |
| J. Sensitive Personal Information<br><br>* Social Security number<br>    <br>* Government-issued identification<br>    <br>* Bank account and routing numbers<br>    <br>* Credit and debit card information<br>    <br>* Geolocation, with consent | * from you when you use our Services<br>    <br>* partners and merchants<br>    <br>* service providers | * provide the Services<br>    <br>* prevent potentially fraudulent, prohibited, or illegal activities, and enforce our User Agreement<br>    <br>* customize, personalize, measure, and improve our services and the content and layout of our website<br>    <br>* send you updates about new products and services that we are offering to customers<br>    <br>* perform other duties as required by law | * PayPal, Inc. and affiliates and subsidiaries it controls<br>    <br>* service providers<br>    <br>* third parties for our business purposes or as permitted or required by law<br>    <br>* law enforcement, government officials, or other third parties |

Privacy Statement

* Privacy Statement
* User Agreement
* Licenses
* Consent
* Cookies
* Helpful Information
* Payment Method Rights
* Approved Business Account Addendum
* Venmo Mastercard Cardholder Agreement
* Venmo Mastercard Privacy Policy
* Cryptocurrency Terms & Conditions
* User Agreement - Effective November 12, 2024

U.S.

* Privacy Statement
* User Agreement
* Licenses
* Consent
* Cookies
* Helpful Information
* Payment Method Rights
* Approved Business Account Addendum
* Venmo Mastercard Cardholder Agreement
* Venmo Mastercard Privacy Policy
* Cryptocurrency Terms & Conditions
* User Agreement - Effective November 12, 2024

Footer
------

### Send & Receive

### Pay with Venmo

### Venmo for Business

### Resources

### Company

### Legal

Venmo is a service of PayPal, Inc., a licensed provider of money transfer services (NMLS ID: 910457). All money transmission is provided by PayPal, Inc. pursuant to [PayPal, Inc.’s licenses](https://venmo.com/legal/us-licenses/). © 2021 PayPal, Inc.

### Send & Receive

### Pay with Venmo

### Venmo for Business

### Resources

### Company

### Legal

Venmo is a service of PayPal, Inc., a licensed provider of money transfer services (NMLS ID: 910457). All money transmission is provided by PayPal, Inc. pursuant to [PayPal, Inc.’s licenses](https://venmo.com/legal/us-licenses/). © 2021 PayPal, Inc.
